Guide to the Michael Lally Papers MSS.361
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Writings, Publishing, and Related Projects, 1961-2012, undated; 30 Linear Feet in 53 manuscript boxes, 3 flat boxes, 3 oversize flat boxes, 1 record carton, and 2 flat-file folders; 7 Gigabytes in 27 computer files; 68 audiocassettes; 4 videocassettes (vhs)
  - Subseries I.C. Readings and Events, 1972-2012; 5 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes, 1 record carton, 1 oversize flat box, and 2 flat-file folders; 68 audiocassettes; 4 videocassettes (vhs); 7 Gigabytes in 27 computer, audio, and video files
    - Album -- Michael Lally: Lost Angels, 2010; cuid36270 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_361_ER_6)
    - Images -- Poetry Reading, 2004; cuid36265 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_361_ER_1)
    - Publicity -- Event Announcements, Fliers, Posters, 1976-2007 (Box 16, Folder 11-14, Box 80, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 1 Left, Flat-file-folder 18)
    - Publicity -- Poetry, 1978-2001 (Box 17, Folder 1-5)
    - Publicity -- Poetry in Motion, 1987-1993 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
    - Publicity -- Readings, 1979-2012 (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
    - Sound Recordings -- Readings and Recording Sessions, undated; cuid36271 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_361_ER_7)
    - Sound Recordings -- Readings, Interviews, Events, 1972-1996 (Box 84, Box 83)
      68 audiocassettes
    - Video Recording -- Herbert Selby Jr.: It'll Be Better Tomorrow, 2007; cuid36275 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_361_ER_11)
    - Video Recording -- Poets Against the War, undated; cuid36274 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_361_ER_10)
    - Video Recordings -- Readings, 1992-1995, 2003 (Box 82)
      4 VHS
  - Subseries I.D. Literary Correspondence, 1963-2012; 8 Linear Feet in 18 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 2 flat-file folders
    Arranged in alphabetical order by file title.
    This subseries contains correspondence with poets, writers, and colleagues, which often include manuscripts and ephemera. Lally's correspondence documents his involvement with the avante garde L=A=N=G=U=A=G=E poet group during their formative years in the 1960s and 1970s, as well as the poetry communities in Iowa City, Washington, D.C., and New York City. Correspondence is especially extensive with those he collaborated with and published through O Press and Some of Us Press (SOUP) in the 1970s, including Bruce Andrews, Max Blagg, Joe Brainard, Gerald Burns, Tina Darragh, Ray DiPalma, Tim Dlugos, Etheridge Knight, Jerome Sala, and Terence Winch. This series also contains four poster-sized message paintings by Sylvia Schuster.
    - Abbott, Keith, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Acker, Kathy, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Adelson, Gloria, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Allen, Karen, 1979-1998 (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
    - Alta, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Anderson, Richard, 1982-2009 (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
    - Andrews, Bruce, 1971-1996 (Box 18, Folder 4-15)
    - Annie, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Ashbery, John, 1974-2000 (Box 18, Folder 17-18)
    - Auster, Paul, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Bachardy, Don, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Bakaitis, Vyt, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Baracks, Barbara, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Beate, 1978-1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bell, Marvin, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Benson, Steve, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Berkson, Bill, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Bernstein, Charles, 1970-1993 (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
    - Berrigan, Ted and Alice Notley, 1968-1982 (Box 19, Folder 10, Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Blagg, Max, 1979-2002 (Box 19, Folder 12-14)
    - Boylan, Nance, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Brainard, Joe, 1973-1993 (Box 19, Folder 16-20)
    - Brodey, Jim, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Burckhardt, Rudy, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Browne, Michael Dennis, 1967-1973 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Burgess-Greco, Suzanne, 1977-2007 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Burns, Gerald, 1973-1994 (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
    - Burns, Theresa, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Callahan, Bob, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Chandra, Sharat, 1969-1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Cleveland, Buster, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Clifford, Wayne, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Coleman, Wanda, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Conde, Miguel and Carola, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Copp, Fletcher, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Corn, Alfred, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Cox, Ed, 1974-1977 (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
    - Crase, Douglas, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Darr, Ann, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Darragh, Tina, 1975-2008 (Box 20, Folder 18-23, Box 21, Folder 1-3)
    - Delynn, Jane, 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Denby, Edwin, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Dennis, Donna, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Dickey, Ralph, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - DiPalma, Ray, 1968-2012, undated (Box 21, Folder 7-22, Box 22, Folder 1-27, Box 23, Folder 1-7, Box 75, Folder 4)
    - di Prima, Diane, 1973-2005 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Dlugos, Tim, 1969-1992 (Box 23, Folder 9-13)
    - Dreyer, Lynne, 1974-1980 (Box 23, Folder 14-15)
    - Drum, David, 1970-2011 (Box 23, Folder 16-17)
    - Elmslie, Kenward, 1974-2004 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
    - Elozua, Raymon, 1971, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Erley, Duncan, 1972-1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Equi, Elaine and Jerome Sala, 1983-1999 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Faville, Curtis, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Fear, Clay (Chris Berg), 1975-1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Ferguson, Anne, 1975, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Flowers, Kim, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Foley, Jack, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Franks, David, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Funes, José R., circa 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Garfinkel, Patricia, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Gerstler, Amy, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Gilfillian, Merrill, 1970s, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Gitin, David, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Godfrey, John, 1982, 2012 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Golde, Morris, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Gongora, Anna Ross, 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Gordon, Jaimy, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Gray, Darrell, 1969-1976 (Box 24, Folder 22-23)
    - Grayson, Richard, 1977-1981 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Greene, Leslie, 1980-2008 (Box 24, Folder 25-30)
    - Greenwald, Ted, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Grenier, Robert, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Griffin, S.A., undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Griffith, Pati, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Grundberg, Andy, 1973-1976 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Guest, Barbara, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Hamilton, Steve, 1976, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Hanor, John and Joan, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
    - Harper, Michael, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Herd, Dale, 1967-1987 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - He Jinian, Lyn, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Hellerman, William, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Hewitt, Geof, 1970-1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Hickman, Leland, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Hilton, Dave, 1974-1979 (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
    - Hollo, Enselm, 1970-1984 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Holman, Bob, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Holzman, Eric, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Hubbard, Karen, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Hughes, Helena, 1978-1985 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Iowa, 1968-2004 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Isherwood, Christopher, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Jones, Jonathan, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Joselow, Beth, 1974-1996 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Kashner, Sam, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Katz, Alex, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Katz, Vincent, 1982, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Kerouac, Jan, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Klappert, Peter, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Knight, Etheridge, 1970-1987 (Box 25, Folder 31-34)
    - Koch, Kenneth, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Kowalewski, Michael, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Lambert, Alix, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Lang, Doug, 1976-2000 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Larcomb, Lee, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 3-5)
    - Leseur, Joe, 1977, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Lesniak, Ruth, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Lopate, Phillip, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Lowenfels, Walter, 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Macadams, Lewis, 1991-2004 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Malone, Kirby, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Mansfield, Stephanie, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Margoshes, Dave, 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Mason, Chris, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Mayer, Bernadette, 1976, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - McCall, Gardner, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - McCourt, James, 1986, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - McCullough, Ken, 1970-2003 (Box 26, Folder 18, Box 75, Folder 5)
    - McKellen, Ian, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Milford, Penelope, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Miller, Bobby, 1983-1997 (Box 26, Folder 21-22)
    - Mohr, Bill, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Moriarty Michael, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Morice, Dave, 1973-1995 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Myles, Eileen, 1977-1990 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Murphy, Merilene, 1990-2000 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - New York City, 1976-2006 (Box 26, Folder 28-30)
    - Nicosia, Gerald, 1995-2007 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
    - Nolla, Olga, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Northrup, Harry E., 1989-2010 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - O'Hara Smith, Maureen, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Oeur, Sam, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Park, Darragh, 1976-1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Perloff, Marjorie, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Pettet, Simon, 1988-2011 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Polite, Frank, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Radical Letters, 1971-1989, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Rain, Jeramie, 1974-1983 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Rector, Liam, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Resta, Susan, undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Rios, Frank T., undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Rorem, Ned, 1979, undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Rosenzweig, Phyllis, 1977-1980 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Rylance, Mecca, 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 20-22)
    - Sala, Jerome, 1983-1994 (Box 27, Folder 23-24, Box 28, Folder 1-8)
    - Schiff, Harris, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Schjeldahl, Peter, 1969-1979 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Schneeman, Brit and Emil, 2004-2010 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Schneeman, Carolee, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Schneeman, Elio, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Salner, David, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Schuchat, Simon, 1971-1977 (Box 28, Folder 15-16)
    - Schuster, Sylvia, 1983-2011 (Box 28, Folder 17-19, Flat-file-folder 18)
    - Schuyler, James, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Selby, Hubert, Jr., 1988-2004 (Box 28, Folder 21-22)
    - 70th Birthday (Lally), 2012 (Box 28, Folder 23-24, Box 29, Folder 1-2)
    - Shrader, Steve, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Silliman, Ron, 1971-1979 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Sjoberg, John, 2010, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Sklarew, Myra, 1972, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Slater, Robert, 1968-2008 (Box 29, Folder 7-15, Box 30, Folder 1-3, Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Starbuck, George, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Sutton, Jim, 1971-2001 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Taus, Roger, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Terrill, Mark, 2005-2010 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Thomas, Lorenzo, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Tillman, Lynne, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Torgersen, Eric, 1969-1981 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Towle, Tony, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Trammell, Robert, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Trinidad, David, 1987, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Trules, Eric, 1979-2000 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, 1993-2011 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Valentine, Jean, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Vicuña, Cecilia, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Violi, Paul, 1975, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Waldman, Anne, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Wall, Eamonn, 1998-2002 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Wannberg, Scott, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Ward, Diane, 1979-2001 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Warsh, Lewis, 1977-1979 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Washington, D.C., 1970-2003 (Box 30, Folder 24-25)
    - Watten, Barrett, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Welt, Bernie, 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Wessels, Kenneth, 1963, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - White, Edmund, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Whiting, Nathan, 1970-1973 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Ramona, 1969-2000 (Box 31, Folder 4-6)
    - Winch, Terence, 1973-2010 (Box 31, Folder 7-12, Box 32, Folder 1-25, Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Wittenberg, Clarissa, 1976-1991 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Williams, Jonathan, 1974, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Worthington, Rain, 1977-2003 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Young, Geoff, 1997-2011 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Youngblood, Doug, 1969-1972 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Zahniser, Ed, 1996-2003 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Zegers, Kip, 1974, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Zu-Bolton, Ahmos, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.E. Publishing Correspondence, 1965-2010, undated; 2.5 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes
    This subseries contains correspondence dating from the 1970s through the 2000s which had been separated from Lally's manuscript files, specifically relating to the publication of his works through smaller presses. Those correspondents with extensive files include Dennis Cooper with Little Ceasar Press, John and Elaine Gill from The Crossing Press, and George Mattingly from Blue Wind Press and Something Else Press. This subseries also contains a large collection of correspondence, mail art, and manuscripts from Jim Haining of Salt Lick Press, of which Lally's book Catch My Breath was one of the company's best selling works.
    - Abbott, Steve, 1978-1980 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Ahern, Tom, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Albert, Barry, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Andre, Michael -- Unmuzzled Ox, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Begley, Mark -- Wake Up Heavy Press, 2001-2003 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Bennett, Joan, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Bové, Robert, 1996-1999 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Bruchal, Joseph -- Greenfield Review Greenfield Review, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Burton, Edwin -- Morgan Press, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Cantor, Ruth -- Literary Agent, 1971-1974 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Coleman, Victor -- Coach House Press, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Colten, Joel -- Hot Water Review, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Cooper, Dennis, 1978-1999 (Box 33, Folder 19-20)
    - Corbett, Bill, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Deahl, James E. -- Shaded Room Press, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Friedman, Michael -- Shiny Magazine, 1990-2000 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Fulton, Len, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Gill, John and Elaine, 1971-1978 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Giorno, John, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Gitlin, Todd, 1966-1971 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Glass, Jesse, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Golden, Mike -- Black Market Press, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Greenberg, Harry -- Some, undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Haining, Jim, 1970-2000 (Box 33, Folder 31-35, Box 34, Folder 1-16, Box 35, Folder 1-9)
    - Hamilton, Brian, 1995-1998 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Hanni, Carl, 1994-1999 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Hartman, Yuki and Vicki Hudspith, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Henkin, William A., Jr. -- Triquarterly, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Hershon, Robert -- Hanging Loose Press, 1980-1999 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Hiatt, Ben L., 1969, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Howard, Richard -- Paris Review, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Inman, Peter, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Jacob, John, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Johnson, Curt -- December, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Katz, Vincent -- Libellum Books, 1986-2010 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Kenny, Maurice -- Contact II, undated (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Kherdian, David -- Forkroads, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Kimball, Jack -- Shell, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Kornblum, Alan -- Coffee House Press, 1975, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Lee, Annabel (Levitt) -- Vehicle Editions, 1980-1984 (Box 36, Folder 1-4)
    - Lehman, David -- Nobodaddy Press, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Leyland, Winston -- Gay Sunshine, 1972-1975 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Mattingly, George -- Blue Wind Press, 1971-1981 (Box 36, Folder 7-8)
    - McClatchy, J.D., 1971 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - McCullough, Frances -- Harper and Row, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - McGahen, John, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - MacNeil, William -- Grok, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - McPherson, Bill -- Washington Post, 1975-1987 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Martin, John -- Black Sparrow Press, 1978-2007 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Merker, Kim, 1969-1978 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Messerli, Doug -- Sun and Moon Press, 1977-1996 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Miller, Tom -- The Nomad Press, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Morgan, Bill, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Moss, Howard, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Muska, Nick -- Toledo Poet's Center, 1975-1977 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Nations, Opal L. -- Strange Faeces, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Neilsen, Pete -- Beatitude Publications, 1995-2002 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - New Prairie Primer, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Nolan, Pat, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Parlatore, Anselm -- Granite, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Paterson, Dick, 1970-1973 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Peabody, Richard, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Powers, Maggie (Magdalen), 1995-2002 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Ribar, Joe, 1972-1975 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Rising Up Angry, 1969, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Ross, Joe -- Washington Review, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Salerno, Mark, 1992-2005 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Saroyan, Aram, 1992-1997 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Schreiber, Ron -- Hanging Loose Press, 1972-1996 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Shepperd, Walt -- Nickel Review, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Shively, Charley, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Skelley, Jack -- Fred and Barney Press, 1981-1984 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Sklar, Morty -- The Spirit That Moves Me Press, 1975-1980 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Spector, Charline, 1983-1985 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Tannenbaum, Janey -- Wyrd Press, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Thompson, Toby, 1977-1984 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Wagner, Steve -- Appeal to Reason, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Williams, C.K., 1981 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Williams, Gil -- The Bellevue Press, 1976-1978 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Wilton, David (Gleep!!), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Winchell, James -- Tropic Harmonica Digest, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Zavatsky, Bill, 1971-1980 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Zivancevic, Nina, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Series II. Screenwriting, Plays, and Acting, 1960s, 1972-2011, undated; 13 Linear Feet in 20 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 2 cartons, 1 flat box, 1 oversize flat box, and 2 flat-file folders; 3 Gigabytes in 24 computer files; 11 sound cassettes (dat); 11 audiocassettes; 42 videocassettes (vhs); 1 videocassettes (betacam); 9 videocassettes (u-matic); 1 videocassettes (video 8)
  This series is divided into three subseries:
  Subseries II.A. Screenplays, Plays, and Related
  Subseries II.B. Actings and Voice Over Work
  Subseries II.C. Correspondence
  Material within each subseries are arranged in alphabetical order by file title.
  This series contains material accumulated primarily while Lally worked as an actor, screenwriter, and playwright in Los Angeles during the 1980s through the 2000s. Files include screenplays, notated actor scripts, writing and acting contracts, publicity, playbills, posters, audiovisual recordings, and correspondence with friends and colleagues in Los Angeles. Electronic records contain voiceover and acting demo samples, and digital images of Lally and castmates in costume on the set of the television show Deadwood.
  - Subseries II.A. Screenplays, Plays, and Related, 1960s, 1978-2008; 8 Linear Feet in 14 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, and 1 flat-file folder; 770 Megabytes in 1 computer file
    A significant portion of this subseries contains edited television show episodes, movie screenplays, and stage plays written, co-written, or script-doctored by Lally, illustrating the many facets of working as a screenwriter in Los Angeles during the 1980s through the 2000s. Notable scripts in which he contributed include the movies Drugstore Cowboy, Fogbound, and Pump Up the Volume. Original works include his autobiographical piece, Fly Boy, a play adapted from his book Hollywood Magic, Chicks With Dicks, and Rhythm of Torn Stars. This subseries also includes posters for Lally's plays Rhythm of Torn Stars and Hollywood Magic; assorted movie and television ideas; and screenplay contracts.
    - Assorted Movie and TV Ideas, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 43, Folder 2-4)
    - Co-Written or Edited By Lally -- Drugstore Cowboy, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
    - Co-Written or Edited By Lally -- Fogbound, 1991, 1999-2000 (Box 48, Folder 4-6, Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Co-Written or Edited By Lally -- If I May, 1987-2002 (Box 49, Folder 2-5)
    - Co-Written or Edited By Lally -- Lost Highway, undated (Box 49, Folder 6-7)
    - Co-Written or Edited By Lally -- Pump Up the Volume, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
    - Co-Written or Edited By Lally -- The Second Coming, 1990-1992 (Box 50, Folder 3-7)
    - Co-Written or Edited By Lally -- Somebody is Waiting, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Co-Written or Edited By Lally -- Star Time, undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Against the Wind, 1984-1987 (Box 42, Folder 3-6)
    - Original Works By Lally -- The Archangels, 1985, undated (Box 42, Folder 7-9, Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Assorted Play Scripts, 1960s (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Beyond Praise, 1986, undated (Box 43, Folder 6-8)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Catch My Breath, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Chicks With Dicks, 1994-1997 (Box 44, Folder 2-8)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Crazy Love, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 9-10, Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Fame Project, undated (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Fly Boy, 1998, undated (Box 45, Folder 3-8, Box 46, Folder 1-8, Box 47, Folder 1-2)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Four Grown Men, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Hollywood Magic, undated (Box 47, Folder 4-5)
    - Original Works By Lally -- The Last of the Tough Guys, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Lee Miller Story, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Original Works By Lally -- The Rhythm of Torn Stars, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Original Works By Lally -- Untitled Movie Idea for Katy Sagal, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Play Posters, 1983, 1989 (Flat-file-folder 18, Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay Contracts, 1983-2001 (Box 38, Folder 10-11)
    - Screenplays for Hire -- Fleas, 1982, undated (Box 39, Folder 2-4)
    - Screenplays for Hire -- Gabriel, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
    - Screenplays for Hire -- Milch Film Project, undated (Box 39, Folder 7-8)
    - Screenplays for Hire -- Milch TV Project, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Screenplays for Hire -- The Milkman, undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Screenplays for Hire -- Peeler (or) Where is West Berlin?, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Screenplays for Hire -- Try A Little Tenderness, 1986, undated (Box 40, Folder 2-9, Box 41, Folder 1-7, Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - Video Recording -- Being Born, in Progress, 2009; cuid36277 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_361_ER_13)